[
 {
   "No": 1,
   "Quiz question": "What flower is the symbol of the sun and the symbol of Japan?",
   "Answer": "Chrysanthemum"
 },
 {
   "No": 2,
   "Quiz question": "What animal has three hearts?",
   "Answer": "Octopus"
 },
 {
   "No": 3,
   "Quiz question": "What color is mollusk blood?",
   "Answer": "Blue"
 },
 {
   "No": 4,
   "Quiz question": "What is the smallest bird?",
   "Answer": "Colibri"
 },
 {
   "No": 5,
   "Quiz question": "What is the fastest land animal?",
   "Answer": "Cheetah"
 },
 {
   "No": 6,
   "Quiz question": "What is the thinnest natural thread?",
   "Answer": "Spider web"
 },
 {
   "No": 7,
   "Quiz question": "Which giraffe legs are the longest?",
   "Answer": "Front"
 },
 {
   "No": 8,
   "Quiz question": "Which animal cleans its teeth after food? (It washes its mouth).",
   "Answer": "Tiger"
 },
 {
   "No": 9,
   "Quiz question": "Which birds have scales on their wings?",
   "Answer": "Penguins"
 },
 {
   "No": 10,
   "Quiz question": "Which animal has green-colored fat?",
   "Answer": "Crocodile"
 },
 {
   "No": 11,
   "Quiz question": "What is the largest spider in the world?",
   "Answer": "Goliath birdeater (spider)."
 },
 {
   "No": 12,
   "Quiz question": "The largest snake on Earth.",
   "Answer": "Anaconda (up to 9 meter)."
 },
 {
   "No": 13,
   "Quiz question": "Which shark has its eyes located 2 m apart?",
   "Answer": "Hammerhead  shark"
 },
 {
   "No": 14,
   "Quiz question": "The largest tree in the world.",
   "Answer": "Sequoia"
 },
 {
   "No": 15,
   "Quiz question": "The tallest trees in the world.",
   "Answer": "Eucalyptus (up to 187 m)."
 },
 {
   "No": 16,
   "Quiz question": "What is the largest lizard in the world?",
   "Answer": "Komodo dragon"
 },
 {
   "No": 17,
   "Quiz question": "What is the largest predator in the world?",
   "Answer": "Polar bear"
 },
 {
   "No": 18,
   "Quiz question": "What is the largest butterfly in the world?",
   "Answer": "White witch"
 },
 {
   "No": 19,
   "Quiz question": "The rarest bird on Earth.",
   "Answer": "California condor"
 },
 {
   "No": 20,
   "Quiz question": "The largest land mammal in the world.",
   "Answer": "African elephant"
 },
 {
   "No": 21,
   "Quiz question": "The largest anthropoid ape.",
   "Answer": "Gorilla"
 },
 {
   "No": 22,
   "Quiz question": "The largest animals on our planet.",
   "Answer": "Blue whales"
 },
 {
   "No": 23,
   "Quiz question": "Where does a camel store its water?",
   "Answer": "In its blood"
 },
 {
   "No": 24,
   "Quiz question": "Do snails have teeth?",
   "Answer": "Yes, a snail has 135 rows of teeth"
 }
]